# **Smith Dbritto**

London, UK | smithdb2910@gmail.com | 07858168197 | My LinkedIn Profile

### **OBJECTIVE**

As a skilled software developer with a passion for innovation and problem-solving, I have a proven record of delivering solutions that meets the necessary requirements. With a strong background in software engineering, I possess the technical expertise and creative thinking needed to develop applications based in Java, C++, databases in SQL and have used MERN stack for Web Development. My ability to work collaboratively with cross-functional teams, communicate effectively, and stay up-to-date with the latest industry trends enables me to deliver great results in fast-paced environments.

### **SKILLS**

# Database & Programming Languages

HTML/ CSS, Java, JavaScript, Python, SQL, C++, Racket

### Software tools

Excel, Figma, Microsoft Office 365, Audacity, Visual Studio Code, Adobe Photoshop

# Communicational & Interpersonal

Effective communicator, Constructive feedback, Socializing skills

#### **EDUCATION**

# Middlesex University | Bachelor of Science

Hendon, London 2018-2023

- Web development: Full stack using MERN (MongoDB, Express.js, React, Node.js)
- **UX Design**: Application of Figma skills, wireframing, mobile app design.
- **Design Secure Systems**: Designing, developing & assessing secure computer systems, Cryptology, security protocol design, threat analysis, security models and security engineering techniques.
- Software Development: Application of C++, Java, Racket, Python, Data Management via MySQL.
- **Object Oriented Programming:** Implementation of real-world entities like Inheritance, Encapsulation, etc.
- Final Grade: 1<sup>st</sup> Class Honours.

### **EXPERIENCE**

### [Technical Experience]

**UCL** Technical Support Assistant

Bidborough House, KingsCross, UK 10/2022-01/2023

- Coordination with different teams in assigning tasks regarding various topics.
- Re-imaging of laptops (reformatting).
- Set appointments for laptop loans.
- Provided efficient ways for the workload.
- Remote Assistance to fix virtual or on-site assistance.

# Middlesex University | SLA (Student Learning Assistant)

Hendon, UK | 08/2019 - 02/2020

- Providing 1:1 support to undergraduates of Computer Science during seminars/laboratory sessions on tasks assigned by the lecturers.
- Support in learning of various topics by multiple methodologies
- Support in better understanding with student as well as the topic at hand

### **Pulse Labs** | Audio Management

- Analysis and feedback for audio progression
- Daily updates
- Working with the AI

Online 10/2018-12/2018

# [General Experience]

Yo Sushi! | Squad Member

Heathrow Terminal 3, UK | 04/2023-08/2023

- Working at Kiosk, along with labeling and restocking the takeaway section
- Hosting the customers and then serving them the food
- Making sushi rolls, hot drinks and cooking in the hot section
- Restocking drinks, serviettes, cutlery and condiments (Ginger and Wasabi)
- Cleaning during closing periods
- Waste management of food during steady periods

# **Empowering Learning** | TA, Cover Teacher & Invigilator

Schools in the UK | 01/2023 - 05/2023

- Maintaining silence of the class assigned
- Assisting and clarification of doubts in known subjects
- Invigilation during exams from classes of Year 5 Year 13's
- Assisting in Teaching with other Teachers

# McDonald's Team Member

Shepherd's bush, UK | 04/2019 - 09/2019

- Customer Service
- Serving customers food
- Cooking, making and packaging the food
- Cleaning during closing hours

#### **PROJECTS**

### **Prediction of Stock Market**

Trained AI to predict the data for the next day using data from past 60 days.

Analysis and Updating with research to improve.

### **Traffic Light Project**

Programmed a traffic light system with pedestrian access and constructed it in person.

# **Surgery Control Panel**

Built functional Java based application with graphical user interface for medical operations.